Brijesh Devgan

 $+919464775949 \cdot imdevgan@gmail.com \cdot linkedin.com/in/brijesh-devgan-8ba41a202 \cdot github.com/imdevgan-8ba41a202 \cdot github.com/imdevgan-9ba41a200 \cdot github.com/imdevgan-9ba41a200 \cdot github.com/imdevgan-9ba41a200 \cdot github.com/i$

SUMMARY

Highly motivated and self-taught Front-End Developer with a strong proficiency in HTML/CSS and JavaScript. Experienced in building responsive and scalable web applications with a passion for solving complex problems and creating delightful user experiences. Committed to staying up-to-date with the latest technologies and best practices in web development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming: C, C++, Data Structure and Algorithm

Design and Modeling Tools: Material UI, Responsive Web Design.

Development: Html, CSS, JavaScript, React Js, MySql, Git.

Soft Skills: Time Management, Problem-solving, Decision-Making, TeamWork, Leadership

ACADEMICS PROJECTS

Valorant Wiki

- Developed a showcase of the popular online shooter game Valorant using React.js as the front-end framework
- Constructed with the help of an API to fetch Up-To-Date data about the game.

Demo

Source Code

Admin Dashboard

 Developed a responsive Admin Dashboard application utilizing React, demonstrating proficiency in frontend web development and component-based architecture.

<u>Demo</u>

Source Code

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Computer Science

2020-2024 7.58 CGPA

Guru Nanak Dev University, Amritsar

Relevant Coursework: Software Design and Programmable Logic, Networking, Operating System, OOPs

EXPERIENCE

Aug 2023 - Sept 2023

Oasis Infobyte, India: Web Development Intern

- Created a professional portfolio website showcasing my capabilities as a web developer.
- Created a user-friendly, responsive and professional Landing Page.
- Built a user-friendly temperature converter application, enabling users to convert temperatures between Celsius, Fahrenheit, and Kelvin accurately.

Aug 2023 - Sept 2023

Bharat Intern, India: Full Stack Web Development Intern

- Created a Video Conferencing website that allows multiple users to seamlessly communicate through videos and text messages.
- Created a content manager application, that stores the data of the user in form of text, images and videos in an organised order.

ACTIVITIES Mar 12,22 – Mar 13,22

Hackathon'22 (Hackathon organised by CESS community of our institute)

• I have participated In two hackathon events as a participant as well as contributer, that helped me to acquire invaluable skills in teamwork, time management, and rapid prototyping